Guide to the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies records, 1966-2014 RL.11552
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies records
1966-2014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (U.S.)
RL.11552
245 Linear Feet
6.9 Megabytes 18 floppy disks with 1228 files; 3 .mp4 video files
The Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (JCPES) is a nonprofit American research and public policy institution, or think tank, founded in 1970 to aid black elected officials in creating effective policy and successfully serve their constituents. The collection includes subject files, writings, publications, photographs, audiovisual materials, and electronic records pertaining to JCPES events, programs, and projects especially of concern to African Americans in the late 20th century. Collection acquired as part of the John Hope Franklin Research Center for African and African American History and Culture.
Arrangement
The Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies Records (JCPES) are arranged into these series: Center Leadership and Administration; Center Offices; Center Institutes; and Electronic Records. Each of the series have been further arranged into subseries. The contents of each series or subseries are arranged hierarchically to reflect the Joint Center's original order.
Biographical / Historical
The Joint Center for Political Studies and Economic Studies (JCPES) is a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization based in Washington, DC that creates policy and programs that improve the socioeconomic status and civic engagement of African Americans. The think tank was founded in 1970 as the Joint Center for Political Studies (JCPS) to aid black elected officials create effective policy and successfully serve their constituents. Founders included the social psychologist Dr. Kenneth B. Clark, and newspaper editor Louis E. Martin. The organization later became the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (JCPES) 1990.
Joint Center scholars, researchers and analysts studies, conducted projects, and programmed forums and conferences covering increased political participation, job creation, workforce development, and health care strategies. Each of the events produced booklets, reports and booklets of use to government officials and the general public. These conversations included the Congressional Black Caucus, African American mayors, and state and local legislators. Interactions with presidential cabinet members, journalists, and foreign policy ambassadors represented the full spectrum of the American political system.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2014.
Collection Overview
The collection is comprised of administrative records for the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, and includes correspondence, memoranda, budgets, funding reports, publications, policy research studies, conference materials, photographs, audiovisual media, and electronic records. Areas of study include healthcare, HIV/AIDS, minority business, television violence, young fathers, education, and minority community representation.
Among its many publications, JCPES published FOCUS magazine from 1972 to 2011, which covered national issues for an audience largely comprised of black elected officials (BEOs). The collection also includes oral histories of Joint Center founders and influencers, interview transcripts, an extensive history of JCPES, materials from the The Joint Center South Africa office which provided post-Apartheid political assistance activities, and original Southern Regional Council publications.
Other materials include interviews/oral histories with founders Louis Martin, educator Kenneth B. Clark who was the first African American president of the American Psychological Association; and McGeorge Bundy, who served as United States National Security Advisor to Presidents John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson on foreign and defense policy from 1961 through 1966. Interviews and transcripts that add historical perspective to African American issues are conversations with Southern black mayors; African American architect and social activist Carl Anthony; and Ernest Green, one of the Little Rock Nine.
Conferences included forums, roundtables, and speeches from notable figures, elected officials, and congressional members including Maya Angelou, Joe Biden, Cory Booker, Edward Brooke, Ron Brown, Carol Moseley Braun, George H.W. Bush, Barbara Bush, Henry Cisneros, Shirley Chisholm, Bill Clinton, Hillary Clinton, Charles Diggs, John Hope Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Maynard Jackson, Valerie Jarrett, Barbara Jordan, Vernon Jordan, Jack Kemp, Coretta Scott King, John Lewis, Eleanor Holmes Norton, Barack Obama, Colin Powell, Charles Rangel, Ronald Reagan, Kasim Reed, Condoleezza Rice, Susan Rice, Donna Shalala, Rodney Slater, Doug Wilder, and Andrew Young. Joint Center historical notes compiled by Darlene Clark Hine are included, as well as Juan Williams' historical publication The Joint Center: Portrait of a Black Think Tank. The files and speeches of Joint Center past presidents Eddie N. Williams; Togo West, Jr.; Ralph Everett, Esq.; and past vice president Eleanor Farrar add insight to the Joint Center's mission of illuminating concerns and trends affecting 20th century African Americans to the legislative influencers most able to effect change.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to audiovisual materials is restricted. Contact the Rubenstein Library in advance to request access to or the production of a use copy.
Conditions Governing Access
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact a reference archivist before coming to use these records.
African American historians; African American intellectuals -- Correspondence; African American political activists; African American women -- Political activity; African Americans -- Civil rights; African Americans -- Medical care; African Americans -- United States -- History; Drug abuse -- United States; Economics -- Societies, etc.; Elections -- United States -- History; Energy economics and policy; Health care -- United States; HIV (Viruses); Minorities -- Employment -- United States; Minority business enterprises -- Government policy -- United States; Racism -- Political aspects -- United States; Welfare economics -- Research; Women, Black; United States. Congress -- Elections; United States -- Congresses -- Senate; Audiocassettes; Electronic records; Negatives (photographs); Optical disks; Oral history interviews; Photographs; Videocassettes; Williams, Eddie N.; Martin, Louis, 1912-1997; Height, Dorothy I. (Dorothy Irene), 1912-2010; Farrar, Eleanor, 1939-2005; Overton, Spencer; West, Togo D., 1942-; Williams, Juan; Jordan, Vernon E. (Vernon Eulion), 1935-; Jackson, Maynard, 1939-2003; Chisholm, Shirley, 1924-2005; King, Coretta Scott, 1927-; Hine, Darlene Clark; McFate, Katherine; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Franklin, John Hope, 1915-2009; Clark, Kenneth Bancroft, 1914-2005; Jackson, Jesse, 1941-; Bush, George, 1924-2018; Bush, Barbara, 1925-
- Center Leadership and Administration, 1966-2014
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual media is closed to use. To request an access copy, please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use these materials.
  Scope and Contents
  Included in the Center Leadership and Administrative series are administrative records in the form of progress and other reports, accounting files, correspondence, historic documents, minutes, by-laws, member biographies, photographs, and audiovisual media. They follow the Joint Center original arrangement, which may be chronological and/or alphabetical. The series is divided into two subseries: Board of Governors (BOG), and Office of the President (OOP). The BOG files relate to board activities, namely the annual dinner and meeting, that date back to the organization's founding in the late 1960s. The OOP files are divided into the offices of Eddie N. Williams, Togo D. West, and Ralph B. Everett, with each having their respective correspondence, speeches, and subject files. The Presidents' subject files were created by the OOP and include files for each of the three presidents represented in this collection.
  - Board of Governors (BOG), 1968-2014
    Access to original electronic and audiovisual materials is restricted. Contact Research Services in advance to request the production of a use copy.
    This subseries consists of original copies of annual dinner programs, correspondence, copyright and incorporation records, trademark certificates, member lists, biographies, conference planning documents, committee and board of governors meeting minutes, reports, research, and agendas. Photographs of major political figures, such as Coretta Scott King and Colin Powell, as well as pictures from Board of Governors meetings and other events can be found here. Audiovisual and digital materials are housed in this subseries. Materials follow the original arrangement, which may be chronological and/or alphabetical. The records for the Public Affairs, Research, Finance, and Development committees are included here.
    - Early history, reports, meetings, 1968-1996
      Materials are arranged chronologically and include documents created when the Joint Center was being formulated at Howard University, and from the first thirty years of the institution.
      - Willingham, Alex - The Founding of the Southern Black Caucus, undated (Box 1)
        This is a working paper.
      - Planning meeting notes, 1968 Dec 7; 3 folders (Box 1)
      - Founding of Joint, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
      - Historical correspondence, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Howard University historical documents, 1969-1976; 1978-1980; 11 folders (Box 1)
      - Annual dinners, 1969-1989; 38 folders (Box 1)
        The materials are arranged chronologically and include memorandums, correspondence and programs related to the first through 12th annual fundraising dinners.
      - Member list, meetings, 1970-1998; undated; 29 folders (Box 25)
      - Research and Information conference, 1970 Jul 14; 4 folders (Box 1)
      - Status report No. 1, 1970 Jul 14; 3 folders (Box 1)
      - Index - Board of Governors minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
      - Status report No. 3, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Evaluation and planning conference, 1971 Jun 4; Jul 12; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Financial statement, 1971 Jun 30 (Box 1)
      - Minutes, member list, correspondence, 1971; 1976; 1987; 38 folders (Box 26)
      - Program report, 1971 Oct 13; 1976 Apr 1-1977 Mar 31 (Box 1)
      - News clippings, 1972-1975; 3 folders (Box 1)
      - JCPS to JCPS, Inc. transition, 1972; 1975-1977 (Box 1)
      - Legal status - Howard and JC, 1973 (Box 1)
      - Legal, 1973; 1987-1988; 1993 (Box 1)
      - Howard University - Joint Center proposal, 1973 Aug 29 (Box 1)
      - Copyright approval, 1974 (Box 1)
      - Proposal for establishing JCPS, 1974 (Box 2)
      - Howard University - Reports to the academic deans and directors, 1974-1978 (Box 2)
      - Incorporation documents - application for tax exemption, 1974 Apr 1 (Box 2)
      - Howard University - annual report, 1975 Jul 25 (Box 2)
      - Report to the Ford Foundation for 1976-1978 refunding, 1975 Apr 1-1976 Mar 30 (Box 2)
      - Minutes, 1976 Mar 24 (Box 2)
      - Legal documents, 1976-1987 (Box 2)
      - By-laws, 1976-2003; 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Howard University - public policy program proposal, 1976 May 17 (Box 2)
      - Decade of Black Political Progress, 1978 Mar 9 (Box 41)
      - Corporate information, 1979; 1984 (Box 2)
      - Trademark documentation, 1979-1994 (Box 2)
      - Annual dinner, correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 181)
      - Public policy planning meeting, 1980 Dec 16 (Box 2)
      - Public policy planning meeting - proceedings, 1980 Dec 16 (Box 2)
      - Public policy research at the JCPS proceedings of a public policy planning meeting, summary, 1980 Dec 16 (Box 2)
      - Ford Foundation - annual report, 1981 Mar. 31-Apr. 1 (Box 2)
      - Proposal to the BOG - Maxwell, James L., 1982 Mar 3 (Box 2)
      - Memorandums, member chronology, minutes, reports, planning correspondence, committee lists, 1983-2010; 36 folders (Box 27)
      - Second quarterly report, 1983 Oct (Box 181)
      - SE Certificates of Approval, 1983-1991 (Box 2)
      - TX Certificates of Approval (Non-Serials), 1983-1993 (Box 2)
      - Third quarterly report, 1984 Jan (Box 181)
      - Impact report, 1984 Feb 28 (Box 181)
      - Fourth quarterly report, 1984 Jun (Box 181)
      - Three year plan 1986-1989, 1985 Nov (Box 2)
      - Overview, 1986 Dec 1-1987 Jan 1 (Box 2)
      - BOG Retreat, 1986 Nov 7-9; 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Patent and trademark certificate of registration, 1987 (Box 24)
      - Monthly memorandum, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
      - By-laws drafts, 1988-1990 (Box 2)
      - Name Change - JCPS to JCPES, 1989-1992 (Box 2)
      - Trademark registration, 1990-2002 (Box 2)
      - BOG Demographic profiles, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
      - TX Certificates of approval 1992 (Box 2)
      - SE Certificates of approval, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
      - Strategic plan, 1994 Jan 1-1996 Dec 31 (Box 181)
      - Trademarks and copyrights, 1994 Feb (Box 2)
      - Conflict of Interest documents, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
      - Copyright Agreements, CF book, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Photographs, 1969-2013
      BOG photographs document the early years of Joint Center and include Board of Governor events, meetings and dinners, and are arranged chronologically.
      - Photographs, 1960s-2000s; 10 folders (Box 3)
        Includes images of board meetings, Eddie Williams, Kathy Vanderhorst, James Baldwin, Jesse Jackson, Coretta Scott King, Charles Rangel, Marion Barry, Colin Powell, John Lewis, Tom Bradley, Kweisi Mfume, Bill Clinton, George H.W. Bush, Hillary Clinton, Maya Angelou, Rev. Joseph Lowery, Vernon Jordan, Jesse Jackson, Boutros-Boutros Ghali, Richard Nixon, Louis Martin, Eleanor Holmes Norton, Andrew Young, Kenneth Clark, Senator L. Douglas Wilder, Maynard Jackson, and Floretta McKenzie.
      - Photographs, 1979-1980; 17 folders (Box 9)
        Includes images of Wendell F. Freeland, Mervyn Dymally, Eddie N. Williams, Richard Nixon, Andrew Young, Marion Barry, John Hope Franklin, Zbigniew Brzezinski, Barbara Bush, Earl G. Graves, George Weissman, Douglas A. Fraser, Darren J. Mitchell, Phil White, Donald Byrd, Eunice Lockhart-Moss, Wendell Holloway, Brenda Girton, George Brown, Bob Bates, Pauline Schneider, Chifornia Cox, Les Well, Anita Martin, Larry Lucas, Robert Brown, Bill Gray, 20th anniversary dinner, Robert B. Washington, Jr., Colin Powell, William H. Gray, David T. Kearns, David N. Dinkins, Vernon Jordan, Dorothy Height, Joe Allbritton, Jesse Jackson, and Bill Clinton.
      - Photographs, 1981; 3 folders (Box 18)
        Includes images of slides, Eddie William, Marion Barry, and Dorothy Height.
      - Photographs, 1990-1993; 14 folders (Box 10)
        Includes images of George Bush (autographed), Vernon Jordan, Jesse Jackson, Bill Clinton, Ernie Williams, Eleanor Norton Brown, Jack Welch, John Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Barbara Bush, George Brown, Vernon Jordan, Julian Dixon, Andrew Brimmer, Eleanor Holmes Norton, Dorothy Height, Eddie Williams, Maynard Jackson, Eddie Williams, Colin Powell, Jesse Jackson, Bill Clinton, Margaret Simms, Vernon Jordan, Jesse Jackson, George Brown, and Junichi Amano.
      - Photographs, 1994-1995; 6 folders (Box 11)
        Includes images of annual dinner, Doug Wilder, Eddie Williams, Sharon Pratt Kelly, Ron Brown, Eleanor Norton, Edgar Wollard, Carl McCall, Dorothy Height, Elliott Hall, Margaret Simms, Vernon Jordan, Dorothy Height, Maya Angelou, Hillary Clinton, and Marion Barry.
      - Photographs, 1996; 12 folders (Box 12)
        Includes images of annual dinner, Juan Williams, Eddie Williams, Elliott Hall, Margaret Simms, Wendell Freeland, Norma Asner, A. Philip Randolph, Al Gore, Eleanor Holmes Norton, LeBaron Taylor, Pauline Schneider, Dexter King, and Joe Allbritton.
      - Photographs, 1997-1999; 7 folders (Box 13)
        Includes images of Colin Powell, Alma Powell, Eddie Williams, George Brown, Bob Eaton, Weldon Latham, Bob Bates, Marion Barry, Earl Graves, Wendell Freeland, George Brown, Jerri Williams, Dennis Archer, George Knox, Dr. David Satcher, Andy Brenner, Eleanor Norton Holmes, Dorothy Height, Togo West, annual dinner with special Al Gore Reception, C. Michael Armstrong, Maureen Bunyan, Paul Berry, George Brown, and Anthony A. Williams.
      - Photographs, 2000-2006; 10 folders (Box 17)
        Includes images of the 30th anniversary annual dinner, Corporate Leadership Forum, Eddie N. Williams, Dorothy Height, Eleanor Holmes Norton, John Lewis, Jacques Nasser, Alan Schwartz, David Jefferson, James Vandenberghe, Christopher Caine, Thandeka Tutu-Gxashe, William F. Winter, John Hope Franklin, William Lucas, Elliott S. Hall, Joe L. Allbritton, David W. Dorman, Gertrude S. Martin, Andrew Young, Juan Williams, Elaine Jones, Susan Taylor, Michael Steele, Alphonso Jackson, Jesse Jackson, Andrew Brimmer, Togo D. West, Jr., Bill Clinton, and Vernon Jordan.
      - Tribute to Congressman John Lewis, An American Hero, dvd, 2000s (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0290)
      - Tribute to Dr. Dorothy Height, dvd, 2000s (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0345)
    - Annual dinner, anniversary events, 1975-2013
      This subseries includes electronic resources of photographs, videos, and publicity related to the annual dinners and events, and arranged chronologically.
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 1975-1991; 70 folders (Box 4)
      - Dais slides, 1990s (Box 19, Disk RL11552-FL3-0002)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 1991-1992; 35 folders (Box 5)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 1993; 42 folders (Box 6)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 1994; 37 folders (Box 7)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 1995-1999; 44 folders (Box 8)
      - 1997 Annual dinner (Box 19, Disk RL11552-FL3-0004)
      - 1997 Dinner program (Box 19, Disk RL11552-FL3-0003)
      - Gala, 2000s (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0254)
      - Joint Center History MTV production for 40th Anniversary Gala, dvd, 2000s (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0012)
      - BOG Electronic media - JC, 2000s (Box 19, Disk RL11552-FL3-0001)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 2000-2003; 3 folders (Box 14)
      - JCPES Dinner, disk 1, 2003 Apr 14 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0063)
      - JCPES Dinner, disk 2, 2003 Apr 14 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0064)
      - Dinner, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0160)
      - Joint Center general reception and dinner, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0067)
      - JCPES Images 0001-0231, disk 1-2, 2004 Apr 21 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0065 - RL11552-OP-0066)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 2004-2009; 11 folders (Box 15)
      - 2005 Dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0221)
      - 40th Anniversary gala annual dinner, 2005 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0222)
      - Annual dinner, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0071)
      - 2005 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0279)
      - Joint Center dinner, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0070)
      - Annual dinner materials, computer disk, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0142)
      - Annual dinner materials, computer disk, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0146)
      - Joint Center Dinner, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0053)
      - Annual dinner images 1-331, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0054 - RL11552-OP-0057)
      - Annual dinner, 2007 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0115)
      - 2008 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0237)
      - 2010 Annual dinner and historical photos (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0235)
      - 2010 Annual dinner and historical photos (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0236)
      - 2009 Annual dinner, 4 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0187, RL11552-OP-0204, RL11552-OP-0207, RL11552-OP-0274)
      - 2009 Annual dinner disk 1-2, dvd (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0311 - RL11552-OP-0312)
      - 2009 Annual dinner disk 2, dvd (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0312)
      - 2009 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0274)
      - Annual Louis E. Martin award dinner, 2009 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0203)
      - JCPES 2009 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0206)
      - Joint Center 2009 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0205)
      - 2009 Annual dinner, disk 1-2, 2009 Apr 21; 2 items (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0315 - RL11552-OP-0316)
      - Annual dinner, disk I, dvd, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0313)
      - Annual dinner, disk II, dvd, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0314)
      - Annual dinner, disk 1, dvd, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0300)
      - Annual dinner, disk 2, dvd, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0308)
      - Joint Center's annual dinner, disk 2, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0208)
      - 2010 Annual dinner and historical photos, 2 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0224, RL11552-OP-0257)
      - 2010 Video produced by MTV 40th anniversary edition (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0289)
      - 40th Anniversary gala annual dinner, 2010 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0219)
      - 40th Anniversary gala annual dinner, disk 1-5, 2010 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0262 - RL11552-OP-0266)
      - 40th Anniversary gala annual dinner quicktime video, dvd, 2010 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0291)
      - Annual dinners and anniversary events, 2010-2014; 12 folders (Box 16)
      - Annual dinner, historical photographs, 2010 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0060)
      - Joint Center annual dinner and historical photographs, 2010 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0062)
      - 2011 Annual dinner Sherry Lassiter (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0259)
      - 2011 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0260)
      - 2011 Annual dinner video, dvd (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0310)
      - Joint Center gala, 2011 May 3 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0261)
      - 2012 Annual gala and board meeting (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0210)
      - Kasim Reed at annual gala and board meeting, 2012 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0061)
      - Kasim Reed at annual gala and board meeting, 2012 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0068)
      - Annual dinner, disk 1-2, 2012 May 1 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0247 - RL11552-OP-0248)
      - Annual dinner choir video, dvd, 2012 May 1 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0016)
      - Annual dinner Mayor Kasim Reed video, dvd, 2012 May 1 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0297)
      - Annual gala dinner, 2012 May 1 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0069)
      - Annual gala dinner, choir, video, 2012 May 1; 2 items (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0320 - RL11552-OP-0321)
      - Annual gala dinner video, dvd, 2012 May 1 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0009)
      - Board meeting and annual gala dinner, 2012 May 1 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0114)
      - Board meeting, annual gala dinner, dvd, 2012 May 1 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0324)
      - 2013 Annual gala dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0267)
      - Annual gala dinner, 2013 May 7 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0113)
    - Annual report materials, 1969-2012; 163 folders
      The Annual Report produced by JCPES covers events, research, and policy and leadership statements. This subseries includes drafts and final programs; program, progress and financial reports; financial statements; program proposals; strategic planning conference materials and reports; and BOG biographies arranged chronologically.
      - Biographies M-W, Louis E. Martin Great American Award, 1969-2007; 5 folders (Box 24)